shutdown of the federal government hours away is Washington a lot of American families are about to pay the price tonight is there any chance
联邦政府小时的停机路程华盛顿很多美国家庭将要付出的代价，今晚有没有可能
major part of Obamacare kicks and Williams have to sign up because they're still confusion tonight take your questions to the woman in charge
Obamacare的踢腿和威廉姆斯的主要部分必须注册，因为他们仍然混乱，今晚把你的问题对女人负责
NBC News exclusive the story behind the unforgettable image from the mall in Kenya young girl for family trapped in the man who came to rescue
NBC新闻独家从商场在肯尼亚年轻女孩的家人被困在谁前来拯救该名男子的令人难忘的影像背后的故事
call of the wild the spectacular event draws family cross the country is this your show about to be cancelled Nightly News
壮观的活动吸引家庭交全国野性的呼唤这是你的节目即将被取消晚间新闻
New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
纽约NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
living it pierced
住它刺穿
clean out the bar in a big last minute change large portions of the federal government shutdown tonight at midnight Eastern Time the first time in 17 years
清理掉棒在最后的大分钟改变联邦政府关闭的大部分在今晚午夜东部时间第一次17年
the simplest way to put it is this the Republican controlled houses passing bills the Democratic control center keeps rejecting the bills would keep the
把它最简单的方法是这样的，共和党控制的房子通过法案的民主党控制中心保持驳回法案将保持
operating while stopping aspects of the new healthcare law and that's where we are life pictures tonight show both ends of the stroma in Washington
而停止新的医疗保健法律方面的操作而这也正是我们生活的图片今夜秀基质的两端在华盛顿
this is in the hands of Congress which now enjoys a 10 percent approval rating from the American people in latest polls this will be a long night
这是国会现在享有10％的支持率从美国人民在最新的民调手中，这将是一个漫长的夜晚
can a lot of government services appear poised to go away at least temporarily is where we begin tonight with NBC Chuck Todd is on the White House lawn Chucky
可不少政府服务似乎准备离开，至少暂时是我们今晚开始与NBC查托德是在白宫草坪查基
good evening Brian Eno temperature means that just friends and family at that point for members of Congress act as a vis hour doesn't appear Congress is any closer to getting a deal to find the Government House Republicans are working on a new spending bill what includes more provisions to try to delay parts of the health care law
晚上好布赖恩伊诺温度意味着只是朋友和家人在这一点上国会议员作为VIS小时没有出现国会更近一步的获得了一项协议，找到政府众议院共和党人正在研究一种新的支出法案包括什么更多的规定，尽量拖延医疗保健法律的部分
send them a cross and a president say anything like that is dead on arrival
给他们一个十字和一个总统说，这样的事情是死在抵达
when is c*** gets 20 the government begins to shut down any of this morning the house and the Senate in Washington speak were in recess
当为c ***得到20政府开始关闭任何今天上午的众议院和参议院在华盛顿说是在凹
Stihl many members found time to play the blame game
斯蒂尔许多成员发现的时间来打的怪游戏
nn essentially holds the American people
NN基本上持有美国人民
Banana Republic in mine says the need to be a John McCain things
香蕉共和国矿山说是一个麦凯恩的事情，需要
the hard ride is demanding a pound of flesh for the actual budget bill how far is passed on Saturday night to keep things going to the middle of December but it also delay the new healthcare law for a year
硬坐正在要求一磅肉的实际预算法案多远，上周六晚上被传递让事情继续下去至十二月中旬，但它也推迟了新的医疗保健法一年
we are not going to mess around with Obamacare no matter what they say they are they gonna get a life
我们不打算更动的Obamacare不管他们说他们谈婚论嫁生活
so when they finally got back to work after lunch today the Senate quickly strip healthcare provisions of the House bill in Senate
所以当他们终于回来今天午饭后上班参议院迅速脱光众议院法案在参议院的医疗保健规定
the eyes of 54 the news 46
54新闻46眼
senator see more concerned about out here people said these kinds of things
参议员看到更关心这里的人说这样的东西
play today blasting Republicans for trying to defund the healthcare law
今天玩爆破共和党人试图对defund医疗保健法
one section
一个部分
loophole today shows Republicans Woodburn Moore blame for shutdown 36 percent with the responsibility of the President 46 percent on Republicans in Washington
今天的漏洞显示共和党伍德·摩尔归咎于关机总统46％的共和党人在华盛顿的责任36％
did a visitor center area right things to cram in Smithsonian visit
做了一个访客中心区正确的事情，在史密森访问补习班
force shutdown remind me personally I blame
强制关闭提醒我个人而言，我责怪
both sides
双方
how long to get to the home
多久才能到家里
it's just partisan politics Dix Hills NY Hilton let you get done let you down no more I get the more you take your heels in
它只是党派政治Dix小山纽约希尔顿让你做让你失望没有更多的你需要在你的脚后跟我得到的更多
late were this evening Brian the president place call to all the congressional leaders including Speaker Boehner their first conversation in over a week
迟到是今晚布莱恩总统的地方呼吁所有的国会领导人包括议长博纳在他们的第一次谈话一个多星期
alright Chuck Todd the White House let's go to the other end of town Kelly O'Donnell what the late of element on Capitol Hill and Kelly all eyes off pan on the moderate Republican summer phone think its a suicide mission to go after a 3 year old settled healthcare law
好吧查托德白宫让我们去镇凯利·奥唐奈的另一端是什么后期元素在国会山和Kelly所有的眼睛离开盘上的温和派共和党人夏季手机认为它是一个自杀任务后，一个3岁去结算医疗保健法
what brand moderate Republicans maybe the Key here they don't want to see the government shutdown and I don't want to see their own party blame for all the harmful effects
什么牌子的温和派共和党人也许这里的关键，他们不希望看到政府关闭，我不希望看到自己的党指责所有的有害影响
New York Republican Peter King is working with a small group of 90 party Republicans more moderate for trying to vote against their own plan from the House Republicans to stop that attracts
纽约共和党人彼得·金正在与一小群的90党共和党人更温和的尝试投票反对他们自己的计划从众议院共和党人停止吸引
and then try to work with Democrats with another time tonight to keep the government opening it is developing its not done yet but there was clearly move among some moderate Republicans who don't want to see the government shutdown
然后尝试今晚要与民主党与另一个时间，以保持政府打开它正在开发尚未完成，但显然存在着在一些温和派共和党人谁不希望看到政府关闭移动
Ashley Sadie their way its going to be a long night Kelly O'Donnell on the hill forest Kelly think so let's take the story out of Washington where the talking is going on with
阿什利·萨迪他们的方式它的将是一个漫长的夜晚凯利·奥唐奈在山上的森林凯利这么认为，让我们的故事出来华盛顿所在的谈话是与正在进行的
what we just saw is already heading home across America after all and could get a lot worse for a lot of families if there is a shutdown over night
毕竟美国各地，我们只是看到了什么是已经回家，并可能变得更糟了很多家庭如果有一个关机过夜
NBC's Kevin Tibbles with us tonight from downtown Chicago
NBC的凯文今晚Tibbles跟我们距离芝加哥市中心
Brian tonight does the hour approaches thousands of Americans who work in and out of government are bracing for the consequences of shutdown
今晚布莱恩请问小时接近上千谁在政府和失去工作的美国人正在准备关机的后果
Chicago protest the possible shutdown Elizabeth 1 hour
芝加哥抗议可能关机伊丽莎白1小时
yeah cuz I'm the only one who is the president a right now
是啊因为我是唯一一个谁是总统的权利现在
she works with you be a mother and grandmother her husband was recently made of cheese frustrated and angry and worried
她与你是一个母亲和祖母她的丈夫最近作出的奶酪沮丧和愤怒和忧虑
Congress need to be turned over somebody's knee and spanked real hard because
国会需要上缴某人的膝盖和屁股实际困难的，因为
acting like small children
像个小孩子
hold us head home not knowing what tomorrow brings Gary
我们抱回家，不知道明天带来什么加里
it's not trust federal workers Navy SEALs superNews near the Statue of Liberty
它不相信联邦政府工作人员海豹突击队superNews附近的自由女神像
will there be any businesses on unless number of the tourist
会不会有，除非数字旅游的任何业务
shutdowns most visible facts
停工最明显的事实
blocking are national parks from coast to coast along with the National Zoo museums in the nation's capital shut down will also put federally backed loans for things like small businesses on hold
阻塞是国家公园从东海岸到西海岸随着国家动物园博物馆在国家的首都关机也会把联邦抵押贷款的事情，比如保持小企业
delay tax audit send refunds and suspend a special Supplemental Nutrition Program for women infants and children difficult for single mother Christina Crowder
延迟税务稽查发送退款，女性婴儿和儿童困难单亲母亲克里斯蒂娜克罗德挂起一个特殊补充营养计划
what are we to do the fetus services include
什么是我们做胎儿的服务包括
essential such as mail delivery traffic control tsa along with tax collection Social Security unemployment food stamps in Passport
如随着税收征管的护照社会保障失业粮票邮件传递交通管制TSA至关重要
one more than $100
1 100美元以上
the president and members of Congress will still receive them
大会主席和成员仍然会收到他们
Cinco they can take that
辛科他们可以采取
does Congresspersons up hx1
做国会议员了HX1
Elizabeth Lytle need to report to work tomorrow to find out if she'll be sent home AR in the sandbox
伊丽莎白·莱特尔需要报告明天要上班，找出她是否会被遣送回家AR在沙箱中
and it is there taking Sanden to the American people
它是有服用三电向美国人民
address to shut down to cost for tween 40 and 80 million dollars a day and I could hit very close to home for many American families Prime
解决关闭成本为40之间，每天8000万美金，我可以打得很接近家​​庭对许多美国家庭首相
Kevin Tibbles in Chicago for us tonight Kevin thanks couple of other notes here tonight Wall bickering overall this Washington politicians have not suspended their own effort to raise money to retain their own jobs
凯文Tibbles在芝加哥，我们今晚凯文夫妇感谢这里的其他注意事项今晚墙整体斗嘴这个华盛顿的政客并没有终止自己的努力来筹集资金，以保留自己的工作
both parties have collected almost a billion dollars in the first half of this year according to federal records
双方已收集了近十亿美元在今年上半年根据联邦记录
tonight they were scheduled to raise even more in a big Gallo for the Republican National Committee in a government building not far from the capital Speaker Boehner was supposed to attend the cancelled instead the GOP turned or former Speaker Newt Gingrich shoe spearheaded the last shutdown we were at the 17 years ago
今晚，他们被安排在政府大楼距离首都议长博纳不远处引起更大的一大加洛为共和党全国委员会本来是要参加注销而不是共和党或打开前议长纽特·金里奇鞋带头，我们是最后关机在17年前
Democrats have their own big ticket event coming up next week
民主党人自己的大票的事件上来下周
at the Fairmont Hotel in San Francisco
费尔蒙酒店在旧金山
featuring House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi and special guest Michelle Obama
特色众议院少数党领袖南希·佩洛西和特邀嘉宾米歇尔·奥巴马
millions of Americans with money in the stock market up and the price for this project fight stocks sign today on wallstreet here in New York
数以百万计的美国人在股市了钱，价格为这个项目争夺股今日在华尔街在纽约签署
worried about the effects of a possible government shutdown all three major indexes down today The Dalles of more than 128
担心政府可能关闭当今的影响三大股指下跌超过128达尔斯
now the other big story of the day the other big deadline at midnight the new healthcare law the center of the showdown in Congress a big part of outlaw war start to take effect tomorrow when people without health insurance can sign up to buy coverage
现在一天的另一大故事的另一大限期在午夜新的医疗保健法律摊牌的中心在国会取缔战争的重要组成部分开始生效，明天，当人们没有医疗保险可以注册​​采购覆盖范围
what are new poll with the Kaiser Family Foundation show 70 percent say they are very or somewhat worried I'll have to pay more for their healthcare or health insurance and 62 percent of those without insurance say they are confused about this new law
什么是新的民意调查与凯泽家庭基金会秀70％的人说他们非常或有点担心我将不得不支付更多的医疗或健康保险和没有保险的说，他们感到困惑这项新法律的62％
are cheap medical editor Dr Nancy snyderman's side down for an exclusive interview with the woman in charge today Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius
便宜医学编辑南茜博士斯奈德曼的一面朝下与女人负责的独家专访今日卫生和人类服务部部长凯瑟琳西贝柳斯
with all the run up time to the end of this why the confusion today and white women not more into the anthem
与所有的运行时间来这到底是为什么今天和白人妇女的混乱不进国歌
well I think it still isn't real for a lot of people and there is a lot of confusion is it your fault day I think we bear a part of the responsibility of not being able to get through a lot of the noise
好，我认为它仍然不是真正的很多人，有很多混乱的是你的错一天，我想我们承受不能够得到通过大量噪声的责任的一部分
what are the big concerns is that as a numbers been taught at they really don't know how things are going to fall in the middle class Mary Lee take it on the chin
什么是爱面子的，作为一个数字被教导在他们真的不知道该怎么事情会落在中产阶级玛丽·李把它的下巴
middle class I would say depending on where that middle class employee work has been taking on the chin
中产阶级不同的地方是中产阶层员工的工作一直走在下巴我会说
when the person says this is the cost of your cable bill your cell phone bill that's not quite true
当一个人说，这是你的有线电视的费用的成本你的手机账单，这不是完全正确
what 6 out of 10 people will have the choice if they choose to make it the choice of a policy for under $100 the back end hurts it's a debate do you want to have
什么6个10人将有选择，如果他们选择，使之在100美元以下的后端疼这是一个辩论的政策选择，你想拥有
protection for basically every check up every visit everything that you do what do you have
保护基本上每个检查了每一个访问，你做什么，你有什么一切
as insulation where you are making a determination where you and your family don't use medical services at much you want to make sure you have protection
作为隔热，你正在你和你的家人不想要确保你有保障的多使用医疗服务的决定
is something really goes terribly wrong what is conceivable to you that the number of a 5000 to 6000 dollar deductible for middle class family
东西真可怕的错误是什么可以想象的到你，一个5000到6000美元的抵扣中产阶级家庭的数量
is a reasonable feasible number well I think that families can make a budget Royce if that isn't something that clearly they can pay for a lot of people couldn't pay for that out of pocket on a lower deductible what does success look like
是一个合理可行的数量以及我认为，家庭可以使预算罗伊斯如果这是不是清楚，他们可以付出很多人无法支付的从口袋里掏出一个较低的抵扣是什么成功的样子
566 s looks like Ave at least 7 million people having signed up by the end of March 2014
566章第貌似大道至少有700万人已经签署了2014年三月底
this is coming tomorrow people without insurance to start signing up to buy it
这是明天要来的人没有保险开始签约买它
tomorrow October 1st the benefits and will kick in January 1st
明天10月1日的益处，并将于1月1日踢
2014 and you will have until March 31st of next year to enroll a lot of people start to walk start looking at healthcare
2014年你将不得不等到明年的3月31日报名很多人开始走路开始寻找医疗保健
what God look at the marketplace in your own state and export your options for your own coverage there are a lot of options out there I think people are going to be
神看在你自己的状态的市场和导出选项，为您自己的覆盖范围也有很多的选择在那里我认为人们将要
little overwhelmed Brian when they start to see what this new market place looks like
有点不堪重负布莱恩，当他们开始看到了这个新的市场看起来像
what time begin with us 24 hour period Dr Nancy Snyderman thank you for always as the President tried to manage this budget showdown at least his end of it all so mad for several hours today with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu just days after the president's phone call with bronze president
我们什么时候开始的24小时内南希斯奈德曼医生谢谢你一直为总统试图管理这些预算摊牌，至少他的这一切结束这么生气了好几个小时与以色列总理内塔尼亚胡今天仅仅几天之后，总统的电话青铜总裁
nothing Yahoo push the President to keep pressure on Iran nuclear program in setting an iron remains committed to the destruction of the State of Israel is expected to deliver that very same message tomorrow at the UN here in New York
没什么雅虎推总统继续对伊朗核计划的压力在设定的铁仍然致力于以色列国的破坏，预计这里提供了非常相同的消息明天在纽约联合国总部
in Chicago tonight several dozen people are injured or not critically thang
在芝加哥今晚数十人受伤或不严格的胜
lake after a frightening train crash during the morning rush
早晨上班高峰期间，一个可怕的火车相撞事故后湖
two trains collide head-on official site of the trains was in a really hard for repair somehow it roll out of the station no one of the controls was doing about 20 miles an hour when it hits the other train head on
两列火车迎头相撞的火车的官方网站是一个很艰难的修复不知何故，推出台站的其中一个控件是做约20英里的时速，当它击中其他列车头
TSP is investigating also tonight the head of one of the largest construction companies in all of Southern California
TSP今晚也在调查中的所有南加州最大的建筑公司之一的头
and his son believed to have been on board in a fatal crash of a twin engine Cessna
和他的儿子相信在双引擎塞斯纳的致命崩溃已经在船上
hangar at the Santa Monica Airport last night federal investigator on the scene says no problems for before the lease before impact
机库在现场圣莫尼卡机场昨晚的联邦调查员说，没有问题的影响之前，租赁前
still head for us on a Monday night in NBCNews exclusive mom and her 5 kids separated
头仍然为我们在星期一晚上在NBCNews独家妈妈和她的5个孩子分离
trappin at mall in Kenya rescue captured an unforgettable image tonight their story of how they got out of hand
倒卖毒品的商场在肯尼亚拯救拍摄的令人难忘的形象，今晚他们如何一发不可收拾的他们的故事
in later Trading Places big news tonight about two of the most well known brand names in all the world
在以后的交易场所的大新闻，今晚约两个最知名的品牌在世界上所有的
as promised we're back now with an NBC News exclusive tonight we hear from the American family that was trapped inside the mall in Kenya gunman all around
如许我们回到现在，我们从里面被肯尼亚枪手商场被困周围所有的美国家庭听到NBC新闻今晚独家
and that family include a little girl rescued by a stranger tonight they are describing for the first time how it is they were able to make it out of there their story tonight from NBC's Ron Allen in Nairobi
和家人包括今晚他们所描述的第一次是怎么回事，他们能够做出来的有一个陌生人救一个小女孩自己从NBC的罗恩 - 阿伦在内罗毕今晚的故事
the Walton family is great Ricky stay together
沃尔顿家族是伟大的瑞奇长相厮守
Ruby mall 4 year olds moment captured in this iconic image that Philip was miles away is North Carolina
红宝石商城四岁的时刻，菲利普是英里这个标志性的形象俘获了是北卡罗莱纳州
family live through a night
家人度过一晚
trap greenhouse to 4 hours terrifying
陷阱温室4个小时可怕
Catherine the three girls just come down the main escalator this escalator in ruins after the port acts
凯瑟琳三个女孩刚下来的主要扶梯扶梯这个废墟中后，该端口的行为
there was allowed
有允许
explosion sound like breaking glass
爆炸声如玻璃破碎
send people started screaming and running then I just grab a girls and started running
派人开始尖叫和运行然后我就抓住一个女孩并开始运行
the two boys were trapped in the grocery store used at store after the Seas the most intense fighting happened here these exclusive photosho the mall ravaged by gunfire explosions and Fire after becoming a battle zone
两个男孩被困在店内使用的杂货店后海最激烈的战斗发生在这里这些独家photosho由炮火爆炸和火灾肆虐的商场成为战区后
horses lay down flat if she could on her stomach in just put her hands in her ears and lay there for hours and just motionless and quiet stay alive
马放下持平，如果她能对她只是把她的手在她的耳朵，躺在那里几个小时的肚子，只是一动不动，安静的住宿活着
local business man up 200 come to the mall to help his brother when he started the Waltons he call to Portia
当地商人高达200来的商场，以帮助他的弟弟时，他开始了沃尔顿家族，他打电话给波蒂亚
stretch my hand out a mental hospital run
伸出我的手出了精神病院跑
she just Brentwood
她只是布伦特伍德
NFL point I thought she was very very brave
NFL我以为她是非常非常勇敢
what do you say to her to convince her to go with teacher
你说什么她说服她一起去老师
think she just knew that it was it was a chance to get out
认为她只是知道这是这是一个机会走出
father for yourself she's pretty much the same age is my daughter
父亲为自己，她几乎是相同的年龄是我的女儿
im a girl out and learn the two boys that already escape the Waltons now share an intense bong
我是一个女孩出去和学习的两个男孩已经逃离沃尔顿家族现在共享一个强烈的奉
you know when that when we met him for the first time after the start in a minute just I put my arms around you crying
你知道什么时候，当我们见到他第一次开始在一分钟后，刚刚我把我的怀里你身边哭泣
afamily with the brave little girl and a stranger who came to the rescue
afamily与勇敢的小女孩和一个陌生人谁出手相救
NBC News Nairobi
NBC新闻内罗毕
credible story we're back in just a moment with the big announcement today about one of the most beloved figures of modern times
可信的故事，我们又回到在短短的大公告此刻对今天的现代时代最可爱的人物之一
the Commandant of the US Marine Corps taken unusual step for the first time since the Vietnam War two generals have been relieved of command in this case because of a Taliban attack a coalition
美海军陆战队的指挥官采取了塔利班的攻击，因为是第一次自越南战争以来两员大将都在这种情况下被解除命令不寻常的举动联盟
base in Afghanistan last year that resulted in the death of two Marines and the destruction of almost an entire squadron of combat aircraft the Commandant General James Amos took the action because the bass have not been adequately protected
基地在阿富汗，导致两名海军陆战队员死亡，作战飞机的总指挥官詹姆斯·阿莫斯采取了行动几乎整个中队的破坏，去年因为低音没有得到充分的保护
Pope Francis has announce table canonize to office processors on the same day this coming Spring St hood for Pope John Paul the second Pope John the 23rd it's even possible the former Pope Benedict the ceremony in late April
教皇弗朗西斯已经公布表推崇办公室处理器在同一天即将来临的春天街罩教宗若望保禄第二教皇约翰二十三日它甚至有可能在前教宗本笃典礼在四月下旬
saturday in Pittsburgh in for football fans everywhere LC Greenwood has died he was part of the legendary Steel Curtain defense and he was a quiet giant who stood six foot six
周六在匹兹堡的球迷随处可见的LC格林伍德已经去世，他是传说中钢帷幕防御的一部分，他是一个安静的巨人谁站在六英尺6
he was a fearsome pass rusher along with Joe green and white white attorney homes made of what was probably the best friend forever LC Greenwood West 67 years old
他是伴随着乔的绿色和白色白律师家园做出什么可能是永远最好的朋友LC翠华西67岁可怕的通行证rusher
its been called the field of dreams for collectors and fans of old Chevys we first show you what was left of Ray Lambrecht Chevy dealership in Pierce Nebraska few weeks back now we can report this weekend auction the mall of
它被称为梦想的领域，为收藏家和旧雪佛莱的球迷，我们首先介绍了剩下的雷Lambrecht的雪佛兰经销商在皮尔斯内布拉斯加州的几个星期前，现在我们可以报告本周末拍卖的商场
ray just couldn't part with the used cars
光只是无法与使用车零件
500 of them somewhere indoors all this time somewhere outside in the elements TopBet of $140
500人在室内某处这段时间以外的某个地方在140美元的元素TopBet
Fox a make up the best brands annual report which not surprisingly ranks the best brands
福克斯一补的最佳品牌年度报告，该报告并不令人惊讶排名最好的品牌
have foot Apple in the number one position worldwide Coca Cola has dropped from first to third leaving Apple and Google in the top 2 slots
有脚苹果在全球排名第一的位置可口可乐已经从第一降至第三留给苹果和谷歌的前2个插槽
the Apple brand name is value now I close to 100 billion dollars when we come back something wild something
苹果的品牌价值是现在我接近100十亿美元，当我们回来的东西野生的东西
beautiful that might just fall victim to Washington
美丽的，可能只是牺牲品华盛顿
are final score tonight is about an event that takes place only at this time of year inside Yellowstone National Park intros American families from all over the country
是最后的比分，今晚是关于一个事件只发生在每年的这个时间内的黄石国家公园的前奏美国家庭来自全国各地
but because of what's happening in Washington right now sadly and someone on believably this year show might be cancelled the story tonight for mendeecees Harris Smith
因为发生的事情在华盛顿现在可悲的是，有人对据信今年的展会，但可能被取消的故事今晚mendeecees哈里斯·史密斯
every fall for you
每到秋季为你
recalled echoes through the valleys in canyons Yellowstone National Park
通过在峡谷黄石国家公园的山谷回声回忆
hearing the elk is one thing but getting a good look at you in the wilderness not so easy
听到麋鹿是一回事，但得到一个很好看你在旷野没那么容易
what boys it worth
男生有什么值得
Ingles a leading the other males know they should not even think about disturbing their hair
英格尔斯领先其他男性知道自己不应该别想打扰他们的头发
Park visitors like Richard bong bugling elk what is seeing old
公园游人像理查德奉bugling麋鹿什么是看到老
Ariat first if you don't know what it is Big Lots Angeles we don't hear that very often
欢迎各第一，如果你不知道它是什么Big Lots的洛杉矶我们没有听到，很多时候
who can help you in Houston where the amp LL
谁可以帮助你在休斯敦地方放LL
fat people injured by apples before we had a lot of cars damaged so you really have to watch when you exit a building look both ways to not something right in front of a boy
胖人由苹果受伤，我们有很多的汽车损坏之前让您真正拥有当用户退出建筑朝两边看不正确的事情在男孩面前观看
even with the summer family traffic long gone
即使在夏天家庭交通早已不复存在
hard to come by
不可多得
Julie McKinnon a trip to Yellowstone is an annual ritual friend Marta card
朱莉麦金农一趟黄石是一年一度的仪式朋友玛塔卡
elk bugle eerie sound through the trees
麋鹿穿过树林军号声令人毛骨悚然
animal quotes
动物报价
visiting Yellowstone the firms are belief in America as a special place what is the government shutdown over the park
参观黄石的公司都相信在美国作为一个特殊的地方是什么政府关闭了公园
and that's a shame NBC News Yellowstone National Park
那是一个耻辱NBC新闻黄石国家公园